Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
=In The Name of Loyalty=
=باسم الولاء=
=Episode 8=
=الحلقة 8=
Kneel.
اركع.
Speak.
يتكلم.
Did you actually dress
هل ارتديت ملابسك فعلا؟
His Majesty in the garment that day?
جلالته في الثوب ذلك اليوم؟
I did.
فعلتُ.
Still lying, huh?
لا تزال تكذب، أليس كذلك؟
Guards!
حراس!
Teach this fool
علم هذا الأحمق
proper palace etiquette.
آداب القصر اللائقة.
Understood.
مفهومة.
You ungrateful fool.
أيها الأحمق الجاحد.
Cheng Ge.
تشنغ قه.
Her Grace personally selected
قامت صاحبة السمو باختياره شخصيا
these books for His Majesty.
هذه الكتب لجلالته.
As His Majesty's favored waiting maid,
كخادمة جلالته المفضلة،
shouldn't you relieve his burdens
ألا يجب عليك تخفيف أعبائه؟
by retrieving these books?
من خلال استرجاع هذه الكتب؟
I've had enough of her.
لقد اكتفيت منها.
She thinks serving His Majesty
إنها تعتقد أن خدمة جلالته
makes her superior.
يجعلها متفوقة.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
She's so full of herself.
إنها مليئة بنفسها.
She deserves a lesson.
إنها تستحق درسًا.
The Eunuch is smart.
الخصي ذكي.
His Majesty will soon arrive for bathing.
جلالته سيصل قريبا للاستحمام.
He commanded
لقد أمر
a saline bath preparation.
تحضير حمام ملحي.
Wait.
انتظر.
Collect them with your left hand.
اجمعهم بيدك اليسرى.
You...
أنت...
You lowly fool!
أيها الأحمق الحقير!
You can't even handle such a simple task, can you?
لا يمكنك حتى التعامل مع مثل هذه المهمة البسيطة، أليس كذلك؟
When did I ever command
متى أمرت؟
a saline bath preparation?
تحضير حمام ملحي؟
Do you know the penalty
هل تعرف العقوبة
for falsifying the imperial decree?
لتزوير المرسوم الإمبراطوري؟
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
Her Grace
صاحبة السمو
ordered Cheng Ge to deliver these books.
أمر تشنغ جي بتسليم هذه الكتب.
Cheng Ge serves as my waiting maid.
تشنغ جي يخدم كخادمة في انتظاري.
Her actions
أفعالها
are beyond your jurisdiction!
هي خارج نطاق اختصاصك!
Scrub this bathing pool
افرك حوض السباحة هذا
until it gleams.
حتى يلمع.
If I return
إذا عدت
to find a single scrap remaining,
للعثور على قطعة واحدة متبقية،
I'll kill you all.
سأقتلكم جميعا.
Understood.
مفهومة.
You,
أنت،
collect with your left hand.
اجمع باليد اليسرى.
Everyone,
الجميع،
the vile Emperor went back on his word
لقد تراجع الإمبراطور الحقير عن كلمته
and massacred Pingxiang.
وذبح بينغشيانغ.
We descendants have sharpened our blades
لقد شحذنا نحن الأحفاد شفراتنا
for this day.
لهذا اليوم.
You are the best of the best.
أنت الأفضل من الأفضل.
It'll be dangerous.
سيكون الأمر خطيرًا.
Make it count with a single strike.
اجعلها مهمة بضربة واحدة.
Don't worry, Master.
لا تقلق يا سيدي.
If it's to avenge the people of Pingxiang,
إذا كان الأمر يتعلق بالانتقام لشعب بينغشيانغ،
death is nothing to us.
الموت لا يعني لنا شيئا.
- Death is nothing!
- الموت ليس شيئا!
Move out!
إخرج!
With all your skills,
مع كل مهاراتك،
why not resist?
لماذا لا تقاوم؟
Until my vengeance is fulfilled,
حتى يتم تحقيق انتقامي،
I can withstand
انا قادر على التحمل
all these indignities.
كل هذه الإهانات.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Why do you...
لماذا تفعل...
You don't need to be so kind.
لا تحتاج إلى أن تكون لطيفًا جدًا.
Too many people died
لقد مات الكثير من الناس
because I couldn't keep them safe.
لأنني لم أستطع الحفاظ عليهم آمنين.
Now,
الآن،
you're the one I trust most.
أنت الشخص الذي أثق به أكثر.
I will ensure your safety.
سأضمن سلامتك.
Don't forget
لا تنسى
I came here to kill you.
لقد جئت هنا لقتلك.
Wasn't my life
ألم تكن حياتي
forfeited to you long ago?
لقد خسرت لك منذ زمن طويل؟
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
Gui.
واجهة المستخدم الرسومية.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
Someone!
شخص ما!
Someone come now!
ليأت أحد الآن!
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
I'll get someone bring the tea now.
سأطلب من شخص ما أن يحضر الشاي الآن.
Hurry! Fetch His Majesty's tea!
أسرع! أحضر شاي جلالته!
Understood!
مفهوم!
Hurry!
عجل!
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
(The dark line is near the Quchi acupoint.)
(الخط الداكن يقع بالقرب من نقطة الوخز بالإبر كوتشي.)
Assassin!
قاتل!
Guard His Majesty!
احرس جلالته!
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
You vile tyrant!
أيها الطاغية الحقير!
- Die now! - Your Majesty!
- مت الآن! - جلالتك!
Go.
يذهب.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
It's not safe here.
إنه ليس آمنًا هنا.
Leave now.
إرحل الآن.
If I leave,
إذا غادرت
how can you seek revenge alone?
كيف يمكنك أن تسعى للانتقام وحدك؟
Since you've given your life to me,
منذ أن أعطيت حياتك لي،
then no one else
ثم لا أحد آخر
shall take your life.
سوف يأخذ حياتك.
Shi Yu.
شي يو.
Shi Yu, are you okay?
شي يو، هل أنت بخير؟
Rest here for a moment.
إرتاح هنا لحظة.
♪Without fate, this dream would fade♪
♪بدون القدر، هذا الحلم سوف يتلاشى♪
♪Without you, my life would quietly end♪
♪بدونك، حياتي ستنتهي بهدوء♪
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting. Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪قدري أو عابر. نسيم الربيع يهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
Come on.
تعال.
Watch out.
احذر.
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
♪Let fate cut like a blade♪
♪دع القدر يقطع مثل الشفرة♪
♪I bid you one last farewell♪
♪أقول لك وداعا أخيرا♪
♪I can't grasp love's depth♪
♪لا أستطيع استيعاب عمق الحب♪
♪Nor hate's pain♪
♪ولا ألم الكراهية♪
♪When we meet again, the snow will melt away♪
♪عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى، سوف يذوب الثلج♪
Hold on a bit longer.
إنتظر قليلا.
I'll find a way.
سأجد طريقة.
Master,
يتقن،
we failed.
لقد فشلنا.
A master came to the Emperor's rescue.
لقد جاء سيد لإنقاذ الإمبراطور.
All our men are dead.
جميع رجالنا ماتوا.
♪Without fate, this dream would fade♪
♪بدون القدر، هذا الحلم سوف يتلاشى♪
♪Without you, my life would quietly end♪
♪بدونك، حياتي ستنتهي بهدوء♪
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
♪Let fate cut like a blade♪
♪دع القدر يقطع مثل الشفرة♪
♪I bid you one last farewell♪
♪أقول لك وداعا أخيرا♪
♪I know not love's emptiness nor hatred's pain♪
♪لا أعرف فراغ الحب ولا ألم الكراهية♪
♪When we meet again, the snow will melt away♪
♪عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى، سوف يذوب الثلج♪
♪One vow, so deep in love♪
♪عهد واحد، عميق في الحب♪
♪I'd give my life for it♪
♪سأعطي حياتي من أجله♪